{
  "items": [
    {
      "question": "Are you pregnant on your first week of pregnancy?",
      "choices": [
        "1st Day of your last period",
        "2nd Day of your last period",
        "3rd Day of your last period",
        "4th Day of your last period"
      ],
      "answerIndex": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the fastest sign of pregnancy?",
      "choices": [
        "Tender legs",
        "Tender arms",
        "Tender breasts",
        "Tender hands"
      ],
      "answerIndex": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the symptoms in the first week of pregnancy?",
      "choices": [
        "Energy",
        "Fatigue",
        "Vigor",
        "Vitality"
      ],
      "answerIndex": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What do 2 weeks pregnant feel like?",
      "choices": [
        "Happiness",
        "Physically Active",
        "Diet",
        "Missed periods, Moodiness, and tender swollen breasts"
      ],
      "answerIndex": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "How soon do you notice breast changes in pregnancy?",
      "choices": [
        "1 to 2 weeks",
        "2 to 3 weeks",
        "3 to 4 weeks",
        "4 to 5 weeks"
      ],
      "answerIndex": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "What symptoms do you have at 4 weeks pregnant?",
      "choices": [
        "Evening sickness",
        "Morning sickness",
        "Afternoon sickness",
        "Midnight sickness"
      ],
      "answerIndex": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which month of pregnancy does the tummy comes out",
      "choices": [
        "1st trimester",
        "2nd trimester",
        "3rd trimester",
        "4th trimester"
      ],
      "answerIndex": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do nipples look like in early pregnancy?",
      "choices": [
        "Whiter and larger",
        "Darker and smaller",
        "Darker and larger",
        "Pinkish and smaller"
      ],
      "answerIndex": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "When we can detect hCG in urine?",
      "choices": [
        "12 to 15 days",
        "1 to 10 days",
        "15 to 10 days",
        "12 to 30 days"
      ],
      "answerIndex": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is fast heartbeat a sign of early pregnancy?",
      "choices": [
        "No",
        "Maybe",
        "Yes",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answerIndex": "2"
    }
  ]
}
